Safa Eren Erdilli

Riga, Latvia ● erenerdilli@gmail.com ● erenerdilli.com ● github.com/erenerdilli ● linkedin.com/in/erenerdilli

PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer with 5+ years of experience in IT, 3 years of which is backend development with <u>Java</u>. I have strong database knowledge and moderate DevOps skills. I am also developing enthusiasm for frontend development and trying to improve myself on React.

Main skills: Java, Spring Boot, REST, Hibernate, JUnit, Oracle, Postgres, Maven, Git, Jenkins, Redis, Docker, UNIX

Currently learning: AWS, React

WORK EXPERIENCE

03/2021 - present Software Engineer

Riga, Latvia Accenture

> Application developer in a large fintech project running on agile methodology. Using Java and Spring. Having end-to-end responsibility, also takes part in deployment and

database operations.

Tech Stack: Java, Oracle, JSF, Maven, Git

05/2019 - 08/2020 Software Engineer İstanbul, Turkey Borsa Istanbul

Responsible for development and maintenance of Market Data Dissemination module of

trading infrastructure in Istanbul Stock Exchange.

Tech Stack: Java 8, Maven, Oracle, Git

05/2018 - 03/2019 Java Developer

İstanbul, Turkey **Gap Year/Personal Projects**

> Created and worked in various software projects. Tech Stack: Java, Spring Boot, Javascript, Postgres

01/2016 - 05/2018 **Oracle Database Administrator** İstanbul, Turkey

Metod IT Academy

Worked as an Oracle Database consultant (remote and on-site) for more than 30 large

and medium scaled companies around Turkey.

Tech Stack: Oracle, SQL Server, UNIX

08/2015 - 09/2015 **Intern Android Developer**

İstanbul, Turkey Intertech Information Technology

> Part of Mobile Banking Application Development team. Tech Stack: Java, Android SDK, Android Studio

EDUCATION

09/2011 - 03/2016 Information Systems Engineering | Bachelor of Engineering

İstanbul, Turkey **Dogus University**

01/2014 - 06/2014 **Computer Science | Bachelor of Science**

Copenhagen, Denmark Copenhagen Business Academy Erasmus Student Exchange Program